The United States is facing a housing crisis: Affordable housing is inadequate, while luxury homes abound, and homelessness remains a persistent problem.
美国正面临一场住房危机：平价住房供应不足，豪宅却比比皆是，无家可归也依然是一个长期存在的问题。
Despite this, popular culture and the housing industry market happiness as living with both more space and more amenities.
尽管如此，流行文化和住房行业却把幸福推销成这样一种生活：既有更大的空间，又有更多的便利设施。
Big houses are advertised as a reward for hard work and diligence, turning housing from a basic necessity into a luxury.
大房子被宣传成辛勤工作与勤奋努力的回报，住房也因此从一种基本必需品变成了奢侈品。
This is reflected in our homes.
这一点体现在我们的住宅上。
The average single-family home built in the United States before 1970 was less than 1,500 square feet in size.
1970年以前在美国建造的独栋住宅，平均面积不到1,500平方英尺。
By 2016, the average size of a new single-family home was 2,422 square feet.
到2016年，新建独栋住宅的平均面积为2,422平方英尺。
What’s more, homes built in the 2000s were more likely than earlier models to have more of all types of spaces: bedrooms, bathrooms, living rooms, dining rooms, recreation rooms and garages.
此外，与早期的房型相比，21世纪头十年建造的住宅更有可能拥有更多各类空间：卧室、浴室、客厅、餐厅、娱乐室和车库。
There are consequences of living big.
住大房子是有后果的。
As middle-class houses have grown larger, two things have happened.
随着中产阶级的住房越变越大，出现了两种情况。
First, large houses take time to maintain, so cleaners and other low-wage service workers are required to keep these houses in order.
首先，大房子打理起来费时间，所以需要清洁工和其他低薪服务人员来让这些房子保持整洁有序。
Second, once-public spaces, where people from diverse backgrounds used to come together, have increasingly become privatized, leading to a reduction in the number of public facilities available to all, and a reduced quality of life for many.
其次，曾经的公共空间——来自不同背景的人们过去常在这里相聚——如今越来越多地被私有化了，导致人人可用的公共设施数量减少，许多人的生活质量也随之下降。
Take swimming pools.
以游泳池为例。
While in 1950, only 2,500 U.S. families owned pools, by 1999 this number was 4 million.
1950年，美国只有2,500个家庭拥有游泳池，而到了1999年，这一数字达到了400万。
At the same time, public municipal pools were often closed, leaving low-income people nowhere to swim.
与此同时，市政公共游泳池往往遭到关闭，让低收入人群无处游泳。
The trend for bigger housing thus poses ethical questions.
因此，追求更大住房的趋势引发了伦理问题。
Should Americans accept a system in which the middle and upper classes enjoy a luxurious lifestyle, using the low-wage labor of others?
中产阶级和上层阶级利用他人的低薪劳动，享受着奢华的生活方式，美国人应该接受这样一种制度吗？
Are we willing to accept a system in which an increase in amenities purchased by the affluent means a reduction in amenities for the poor?
富人购买的便利设施增多，就意味着穷人能享有的便利设施减少，我们愿意接受这样一种制度吗？
I believe neither is acceptable.
我认为两者都不可接受。
We must change the way we think: living well does not need to mean having more private spaces; instead, it could mean having more public spaces.
我们必须改变思维方式：过得好不必意味着拥有更多私人空间，而是可以意味着拥有更多公共空间。
A better goal than building bigger houses for some is to create more publicly accessible spaces and amenities for all.
比起为一部分人建造更大的房子，更好的目标是为所有人创造更多向公众开放的空间和便利设施。